export const chapter = "Chapter - 17:Towards the Path of Freedom  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "What act passed in 1919 disunited the Indians and dissatisfied the Congress and Indians?",
        optionA: "Government of India Act 1919",
        optionB: "Rowlatt Act",
        optionC: "Simon Commission",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What was the main trigger for the Jallianwala Bagh Massacre in Amritsar in 1919?",
        optionA: "A religious procession",
        optionB: "A peaceful public meeting",
        optionC: "A farmers' protest",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question: "What did General Dyer do at the Jallianwala Bagh Massacre?",
        optionA: "Ordered the protesters to disperse",
        optionB: "Opened fire on the crowd",
        optionC: "Negotiated with the protesters",
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What did Mahatma Gandhi use as his primary weapon during the Gandhian Phase of the Nationalist Movement?",
        optionA: "Non-violence and Satyagraha",
        optionB: "Armed rebellion",
        optionC: "Boycotts and strikes",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which movement marked a new awakening in the Indian Independence Movement and was led by Mahatma Gandhi and the Indian National Congress?",
        optionA: "Quit India Movement",
        optionB: "Civil Disobedience Movement",
        optionC: "Non-cooperation Movement",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What event led to the withdrawal of the Non-cooperation Movement in 1922?",
        optionA: "Chauri Chaura Incident",
        optionB: "Simon Commission",
        optionC: "Jallianwala Bagh Massacre",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who were the important leaders of the Hindustan Socialist Republican Army, known for their non-violent approach and self-sacrifice?",
        optionA: "Bhagat Singh and Chandra Shekhar Azad",
        optionB: "Ram Prasad Bismil and Roshan Singh",
        optionC: "Ashafaquallah Khan and Rajendra Lahiri",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What commission was appointed by the British government in 1927, leading to widespread protests in India?",
        optionA: "Simon Commission",
        optionB: "Cabinet Mission",
        optionC: "Rowlatt Commission",
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which movement did Mahatma Gandhi initiate by organizing the Salt Satyagraha March in 1930?",
        optionA: "Quit India Movement",
        optionB: "Civil Disobedience Movement",
        optionC: "Dandi March",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Who was the leader of the Indian National Army and known for the slogans 'Jai Hind' and 'Dilli Chalo'?",
        optionA: "Mahatma Gandhi",
        optionB: "Jawaharlal Nehru",
        optionC: "Subhash Chandra Bose",
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "After the First World War, Indian soldiers returned with new ideas of ___________.",
        options: ["Unity", "Independence", "Trade"],
        correctAnswer: "Independence",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Government of India Act 1919 aimed to ___________ the Indians.",
        options: ["Unite", "Divide", "Educate"],
        correctAnswer: "Divide",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Rowlatt Act, passed in March 1919, allowed the arrest of individuals on the basis of ___________.",
        options: ["Suspicion", "Evidence", "Request"],
        correctAnswer: "Suspicion",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The Jallianwala Bagh Massacre occurred during the ___________ festival.",
        options: ["Diwali", "Baisakhi", "Holi"],
        correctAnswer: "Baisakhi",
      },
      {
        question:
          "General Dyer opened fire on the crowd in Jallianwala Bagh without any ___________.",
        options: ["Warning", "Reason", "Support"],
        correctAnswer: "Warning",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The third and final phase of the Nationalist Movement [1917-1947] is known as the ___________ Phase.",
        options: ["Revolutionary", "Gandhian", "British"],
        correctAnswer: "Gandhian",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Mahatma Gandhi began his experiments with Satyagraha against the oppressive European indigo planters in ___________ in 1917.",
        options: ["Mumbai", "Champaran", "Kolkata"],
        correctAnswer: "Champaran",
      },
      {
        question: "The Non-cooperation Movement was led by ___________.",
        options: ["Subhash Chandra Bose", "Jawaharlal Nehru", "Mahatma Gandhi"],
        correctAnswer: "Mahatma Gandhi",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The last stage of the movement was the ___________ Movement.",
        options: ["Non-cooperation", "Civil Disobedience", "Revolutionary"],
        correctAnswer: "Civil Disobedience",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The British government appointed a commission in 1927 under the chairmanship of ___________ to handle law and order situation in India.",
        options: ["Mahatma Gandhi", "Sir John Simon", "Jawaharlal Nehru"],
        correctAnswer: "Sir John Simon",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "Jaisalmer is famous for its unique buildings made of golden sandstone.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The climate of Jodhpur is characterized by a lot of rainfall.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Barmer is known for its wood-carving, pottery, and block-printed fabrics.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "Bikaner is situated to the west of Jaisalmer.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "The Great Indian Desert is also known as the Thar Desert.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Jodhpur is often referred to as the 'Sun City' due to its sunny weather.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The people of the Western Desert are unfriendly and unwelcoming to visitors.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Crops like bajra, jowar, and til are grown in Jaisalmer due to its arid climate.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The carpet weaving industry is one of the renowned industries of Rajasthan.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question: "The discovery of fire was insignificant for early humans.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
